BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Correspondence, 1944-1977; 1
  - Baylor University, 1947-1967; 4
    - Drama Department, 1948-1951 (Box 145, Folder 23)
    - Ex-Students, 1950-1951 (Box 145, Folder 24)
    - Ex-Students, 1951 (Box 145, Folder 25)
    - Ex-Students Association (1 of 3), 1951-1952 (Box 145, Folder 26)
    - Ex-Students Association (2 of 3), 1951-1952 (Box 145, Folder 27)
    - Ex-Students Association (3 of 3), 1951-1952 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Ex-Students Association (1 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Ex-Students Association (2 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Ex-Students Association, 1955-1956 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Ex-Students Association, 1961-1963 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Ex-Students — Baylor Clubs, 1961 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Ex-Students — Baylor Line, 1960 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Ex-Students — Baylor Line Letters to the Editor, 1960 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Ex-Students — Baylor Line, 1962 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Ex-Students Association, 1973-1976 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Faculty, 1956 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Focus Week, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Focus Week, 1962 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Football Welcomes, 1959 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Founder’s Day February 1, 1845, 1950 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Gator Bowl December 31 (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Gator Bowl December 31 (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Gifts to Baylor, 1949 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Girl’s Dormitory New, 1951-1952 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Concerning Convocation (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Concerning Convocation (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Convocation October 16th and 17th Those Refusing Invitations (1 of 6), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 23)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Convocation October 16th and 17th Those Refusing Invitations (2 of 6), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 24)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Convocation October 16th and 17th Those Refusing Invitations (3 of 6), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Convocation October 16th and 17th Those Refusing Invitations (4 of 6), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 26)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Convocation October 16th and 17th Those Refusing Invitations (5 of 6), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Convocation October 16th and 17th Those Refusing Invitations (6 of 6), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 28)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Convocation October 16th and 17th Those Attending (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 29)
    - Greater Baylor Campaign-Convocation October 16th and 17th Those Attending (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 30)
    - Hong Kong, 1957 (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - Honorary Degrees (1 of 4), 1949-1950 (Box 146, Folder 32)
    - Honorary Degrees (2 of 4), 1949-1950 (Box 146, Folder 33)
    - Honorary Degrees (3 of 4), 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Honorary Degrees (4 of 4), 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Honorary Degrees (1 of 2), 1951 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Honorary Degrees (2 of 2), 1951 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1953 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1957 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Honorary Degree Committee, 1959 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Human Relations (1 of 2), 1951 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Human Relations (2 of 2), 1951 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Letters of Appreciation for Joining Faculty (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Letters of Appreciation for Joining Faculty (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Naval ROTC (1 of 2), 1948-1951 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Naval ROTC (2 of 2), 1948-1951 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - New Dormitory Program, 1950 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Ogilvie Case (1 of 6), 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Ogilvie Case (2 of 6), 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Ogilvie Case (3 of 6), 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Ogilvie Case (4 of 6), 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Ogilvie Case (5 of 6), 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Ogilvie Case (6 of 6), 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Orange Bowl (1 of 2), 1951-1952 (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Orange Bowl (2 of 2), 1951-1952 (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Publicity-Athletic, 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - Reports on Contacts, 1960 (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Religious Education Building Fund, 1948 (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - Requests-General (1 of 4), 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - Requests-General (2 of 4), 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - Requests-General (3 of 4), 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 28)
    - Requests-General (4 of 4), 1949-1950 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Scholarships, 1958 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Scholarship Funds, 1949-1950 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Scholarship-Jefferson Davis, 1948 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - School of Business, 1959-1960 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - School of Nursing, undated (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Speech Requests, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Stadium Campaign (1 of 4), 1951 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Stadium Campaign (2 of 4), 1951 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Stadium Campaign (3 of 4), 1951 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Stadium Campaign (4 of 4), 1951 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Student Counseling and Testing Center, 1960 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Student Organizations, 1961-1963 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Student Problems, 1951 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Student Council, 1951 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Student Council, 1953 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Students-Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Students-Prospective (1 of 2), 1951 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Students-Prospective (2 of 2), 1951 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Tenth Anniversary Greetings (bound), 1958 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - W.R. White Lectureship Fund, 1964 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Working Permission for Students, 1953 (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Working Permission for Students, 1954 (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Women’s Infirmary, 1949 (Box 148, Folder 23)
- Baylor University Records, 1942-1977, undated; 2
  This series is a paper collection of the records from the Office of the President, Chancellor, and President Emeritus. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - A Report and Explanation of the Activities of the Student Counseling and Testing Center, 1955-1959 (Box 148, Folder 24)
  - A Study of Physical Plant Facilities, 1960 (Box 148, Folder 25)
  - A Survey Analysis and Plan for Baylor University, 1960 January (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Academic Discipline Committee (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - The Accreditation of Baylor University and the Schools and the Departments, 1959 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Committee, 1953 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Committee, 1955 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Committee, 1958 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Committee Report, 1956 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Air Force Reserve Officer Training Corps (AFROTC), 1956-1957 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - AFROTC, 1957 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - AFROTC, 1961 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Air Science (ROTC), 1960-1961 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - American Airlines Campus Representative, undated (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - American Association of University Professors Baylor Chapter, 1966-1967 (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - American Auto Association, undated (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - American Ideals Conference, 1958 (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - American Ideals Conference and Inauguration, 1961 (Box 149, Folder 18)
  - Analysis of Student Body Classification, 1959 (Box 149, Folder 19)
  - Ann Williams Pre-Paid Tuition, 1959-1965 (Box 149, Folder 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 149, Folder 21)
  - Annuities and Baylor, undated (Box 149, Folder 22)
  - February to April Travel Expense, 1962 February-April (Box 149, Folder 23)
  - Armstrong-Browning Building, 1948-1951 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Armstrong-Browning Building, 1951 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong-Browning Building, 1952 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong-Browning Building, 1953 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong-Browning Building, 1954-1955 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Armstrong-Browning Building, 1955-1956 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Armstrong-Browning Library, 1960 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Armstrong-Browning Library, undated (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Art Department, 1961 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Art Department, undated (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Assorted Baylor Reports, undated (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Athletics, 1949-1951 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Athletics Department, 1950-1951 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Athletics Department, 1953 (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - Athletics Department, 1956-1957 (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - Athletics Department, 1958-1959 (Box 150, Folder 16)
  - Athletics Department, 1961-1963 (Box 150, Folder 17)
  - Athletics Department, 1961 (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Attendance Reports-Mr. Grant, 1949-1950 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Attendance Reports-Grant, 1951 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Audit Report Baylor Hospital, 1955 August 31 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Baccalaureate Sermon Commencement May 1970, 1970 May (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas Baylor University, 1957 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1961-1963 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Baptist Student Union of Baylor University, 1965, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Basketball, 1960-1961 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Basketball, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Annuity Plan, 1955 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Baylor at Waco Statistics, 1960 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Baylor ‘B’ Association, 1959-1960 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Baylor ‘B’ Association, 1960-1961 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Dallas 1 (1 of 2), 1949-1950 (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Dallas 1 (2 of 2), 1949-1950 (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees-Dallas 2, 1949-1950 (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, 1951 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees, 1952 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees, 1954 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of Meeting of the Houston Executive Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of Dallas Executive Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, 1954-1956 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of the Dallas Executive Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of the Houston Executive Committee, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of the Houston Executive Committee, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of the Dallas Executive Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees (1 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees (2 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of the Houston Executive Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of Dallas Executive Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1958 February 17 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1958 May 26 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, 1958-1959 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes of Dallas Executive Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Committee, 1959 January 19 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1959 May 4 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1959 April 24 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees, 1959-1960 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 1959 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1959 September 11 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1959 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1960 October 3 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1961 January 16 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1961 March 15 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1961 April 10 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1961 June 5 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1961 September 15 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1962 January 15 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1962 March 22 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1962 June 11 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1962 September 14 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1963 January 14 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees-Agenda Houston Executive Committee, 1963 June 3 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee, 1963 September 24 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee, 1965 June 9 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee, 1965 October 11 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee, 1965 November 10 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee, 1966 January 10 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee, 1966 February 9 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee, 1966 March 14 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee, 1967 November 13 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees, 1959, 1965, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Board of Trustees Houston Executive Committee Informational Material, undated (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Books: A Selective List of Acquisitions, 1950-1951 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Books: A Selective List of Acquisitions, 1959 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Books: A Selective List of Acquisitions, 1961 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Books: A Selective List of Acquisitions, 1962-1963 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Book Store, 1958-1959 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Book Store, 1960-1961 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Book Store, 1961-1962 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Book Store, 1962 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Book Store, 1963-1966 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Business Studies, 1960 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - The Baylor Challenge, 1960, 1964 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - The Baylor Challenge Report for Trustee Meeting, 1960 October (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Chamber of Commerce, 1960-1961 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Chapel Programs Political, 1960 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Chapel Programs Political, 1961-1962 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Conference Material, 1958, 1960 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Dental Journal, 1960 Spring (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (1 of 3), 1948-1950 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (2 of 3), 1948-1950 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (3 of 3), 1948-1950 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (1 of 3), 1950-1952 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (2 of 3), 1950-1952 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (3 of 3), 1950-1952 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (1 of 3), 1951 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (2 of 3), 1951 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (3 of 3), 1951 (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (1 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (2 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas (2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas, 1959-1960 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas, 1960-1961 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Dental School at Dallas, 1962 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Freedom Speech Pamphlets, 1957 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Graduate Council, 1960 September 29 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 5), undated (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 5), undated (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 5), undated (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (4 of 5), undated (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (5 of 5), undated (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas Records, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 3), 1948-1950 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 3), 1948-1950 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 3), 1948-1950 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas: Audit Report, 1951 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 6), 1953 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 6), 1953 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 6), 1953 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (4 of 6), 1953 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (5 of 6), 1953 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (6 of 6), 1953 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 5), 1952 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 5), 1952 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 5), 1952 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (4 of 5), 1952 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (5 of 5), 1952 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (4 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (5 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (6 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (7 of 7), 1954-1955 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 7), 1955-1956 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 7), 1955-1956 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 7), 1955-1956 (Box 161, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (4 of 7), 1955-1956 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (5 of 7), 1955-1956 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (6 of 7), 1955-1956 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (7 of 7), 1955-1956 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (4 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (5 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 6), 1958-1959 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 6), 1958-1959 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 6), 1958-1959 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (4 of 6), 1958-1959 (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (5 of 6), 1958-1959 (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (6 of 6), 1958-1959 (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (1 of 3), 1959 (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (2 of 3), 1959 (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (3 of 3), 1959 (Box 162, Folder 18)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (Baylor Medical Center), 1959 (Box 162, Folder 19)
  - Baylor Hospital at Dallas (Baylor Medical Center), 1961-1962 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Lodge, undated (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (1 of 3), 1952 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (2 of 3), 1952 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (3 of 3), 1952 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston, 1953 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (1 of 4), 1954-1955 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (2 of 4), 1954-1955 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (3 of 4), 1954-1955 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (4 of 4), 1954-1955 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (1 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (2 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (3 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston, 1957-1958 (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston, 1958-1959 (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston, 1959-1960 (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 163, Folder 20)
  - Baylor Medical School at Houston, 1961-1962 (Box 163, Folder 21)
  - Baylor Mixed, 1961 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Mixed, 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Press, 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Press, 1961-1965 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Baylor Stadium Corporation, 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Stadium Corporation, 1961-1963 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Sustaining Fund, 1955 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Sustaining Fund, 1956-1957 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Sustaining Fund, 1957 (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Survey Recommendations, undated (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Trustee Bulletin (1 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Trustee Bulletin (2 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Trustee Bulletin (3 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Trustee Bulletin (4 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Trustee Bulletin (5 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Trustee Mailing List, 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 16)
  - Baylor University, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 17)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 18)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 164, Folder 19)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 164, Folder 20)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1962-1975 (Box 164, Folder 21)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1964-1965 (Box 164, Folder 22)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1966-1975 (Box 164, Folder 23)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation-Development (1 of 4), 1966-1977 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation-Development (2 of 4), 1966-1977 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation-Development (3 of 4), 1966-1977 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation-Development (4 of 4), 1966-1977 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Bearagraphs, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - “Blood, Sweat and Tears” Baylor’s One-Hundred Twenty Five Years by W.R. White, 1969 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Books 1, 1959 (Box 165, Folder 7)